<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-08T19:06:29-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">José M. Salgado</title><subtitle>Welcome to my website! Here, you can find my portfolio and the services I offer. You can also read my blog and find my qualifications and contact information.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Darkest Hour, 2017 (film review)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/reviews/2023/07/29/Darkest-Hour.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Darkest Hour, 2017 (film review)" /><published>2023-07-29T17:30:35-07:00</published><updated>2023-07-29T17:30:35-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/reviews/2023/07/29/Darkest-Hour</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/reviews/2023/07/29/Darkest-Hour.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;darkest-hour-2017&quot;&gt;Darkest Hour, 2017&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;He mobilized the English language and sent it into battle.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Quote from an ambiguous origin, often used to describe Churchill’s ability with words&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Darkest Hour” illustrates the relentless sequence of events happening in May and June 1940, nearly leaving Europe under Nazi control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Denmark, Norway, the Netherlands, and Belgium fell within weeks. The Allies fled continental Europe through Dunkirk, leaving France ready to surrender. German military superiority was unquestionable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With an ambivalent parliament, a dubious king, and a hesitant America, Churchill only had his words, and his words he used. In his speech, “We Shall Fight on the Beaches,” delivered to the House of Commons on June 4, 1940, Churchill articulated the attitude that the Allies needed to resolve. Churchill, one of the most flamboyant characters in history, is exquisitely interpreted by Gary Oldman, a performance that earned him an Academy Award.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Reviews" /><summary type="html">Darkest Hour, 2017</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Greenlights, 2020 (audiobook review)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/reviews/2022/12/25/Green-Lights.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Greenlights, 2020 (audiobook review)" /><published>2022-12-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-12-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/reviews/2022/12/25/Green-Lights</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/reviews/2022/12/25/Green-Lights.html">&lt;p&gt;This is the self-narrated story of Matthew McConaughey, the person, not the actor. The life of this man and the story of the book is guided by a marked principle; the concern with getting too comfortable and taking the challenge as the only way possible to move forward. Matthew considers that the &lt;em&gt;McConaissance&lt;/em&gt; is for everyone who finds out that the call to self-knowledge through adventure is not an option but a moral imperative. Imprinted with his iconic charisma, the audio narration is a highly entertaining story of how Matthew developed his own character.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Reviews" /><summary type="html">This is the self-narrated story of Matthew McConaughey, the person, not the actor. The life of this man and the story of the book is guided by a marked principle; the concern with getting too comfortable and taking the challenge as the only way possible to move forward. Matthew considers that the McConaissance is for everyone who finds out that the call to self-knowledge through adventure is not an option but a moral imperative. Imprinted with his iconic charisma, the audio narration is a highly entertaining story of how Matthew developed his own character.</summary></entry></feed>